## Don Alfons Nisnoni Resume

#### **PERSONAL DATA**



Date of Birth: 18 September 1995 (26 years old)

Address: Semangka street, Amnesi, Kota Raja sub-district, Kupang city, East

Nusa Tenggara, Indonesia **Phone:** +6283809705594

**Preffered Position:** Front-end Web Developer

Email: donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com

Website: donnisnoni.github.io

**GitHub:** donnisnoni **LinkedIn:** donnisnoni

## Hello!

**SUMMARY** 

Hi there! My name is Don Alfons Nisnoni. I'm a front-end web developer from Indonesia.

I mostly do front-end web development on my daily programming activity. I learn web development since 2015 when *web programming* lecture is introduced to me on my campus. I falling in love with web development and always looking forward building things and product with it.

#### Fresh graduate

I just graduated back in november 2020 with GPA of 3.44. Actually, I finished my college on december 2019. But because of COVID-19 pandemic, the graduation ceremony is postponed.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Degree of Computer Science @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - **GPA: 3.44** - Graduated on Nov 2020 due COVID-19

#### **SKILLS**

Thing's that I've touch so far:

#### Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG

#### Databases:

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

## **Programming Languages:**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP

## Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, React, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

## Technique:

Responsive Web Desing, a11y, i18n, PWA

#### **EXPERIENCES**

## Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

- Build a website for improve student's online services
- Upgrade & improve campus main website
- Create work email for lecturer's
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI
- Upgrade campus tech stacks

## Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2021 - May 2021 @ **Vlingo** 

• Implementing vlingo/auth UI

## Front-End Web Developer

May 2021 - Present @ Bali Casa Villas